Finding Aid for the J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Additional Photographs, circa 1910-1971, VIII.; 236 photographs
  - Claudia Muzio as Desdemona in Otello, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Daguerre (Chicago, Ill.) (Box 35, Item C35-089)
  - Magda Olivero as Adriana Lecouvreur, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-090)
  - Leontyne Price as Cio-Cio-San and Mildred Miller as Suzuki in Madame Butterfly, 1961?, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 35, Item C35-091)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as Eva and Hans Hopf as Stolzing in Die Meistersinger von Nürnberg, 1951, 1 black and white photograph; Renner, Eduard, 1891-1952 (Box 35, Item C35-092)
  - Tullio Serafin (left) with unidentified male, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-093)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Santuzza in Cavalleria rusticana, 1954-1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-094)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Santuzza in Cavalleria rusticana, 1954-1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-095)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Rosina in Barber of Seville, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Reale (Rome, Italy) (Box 35, Item C35-096)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Cio-Cio-San in Madame Butterfly, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Troncone (Naples, Italy) (Box 35, Item C35-097)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Cio-Cio-San in Madame Butterfly, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Troncone (Naples, Italy) (Box 35, Item C35-098)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Desdemona and Mario Del Monaco as Otello in Otello, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 35, Item C35-099)
  - Tullio Serafin (left), Renata Tebaldi, and Tito Gobbi in rehearsal of Falstaff, 1958, 1 color photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 35, Item C35-100)
  - Tullio Serafin (left), Renata Tebaldi, and Tito Gobbi in rehearsal of Falstaff, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 35, Item C35-101)
  - Theodore Thomas, conductor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; A.W. Elson & Co. (Box 35, Item C35-102)
  - Michael Tilson Thomas, 1999?, 1 black and white photograph; McCarthy, Terrence (Box 35, Item C35-103)
  - Martial Singher as Dapertutto in The Tales of Hoffmann, 1943, 1 black and white photograph; Franklin Photos (Firm: New York, N.Y.) (Box 35, Item C35-104)
  - Arturo Toscanini, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-105)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
Singers--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs; Music-halls--Photographs; Opera--Production and direction--Photographs; Operatic scenes--Photographs; Musical groups--Photographs; Composers--Photographs
Genres
Photographs; Portraits
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
J. Warren Perry Collection of Ballet Photographs, circa 1910-1960
Mus. Arc. 3.2
A collection of 300 black and white photographs of ballet dancers and choreographers, chiefly from the 1950s.